Guide to the Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student Papers, 1877-1909; Series VII
  Luker, Herbert, "On the Anatomy of Three West Indian Epiphytes" 9pp, box 90, folder 995 was reported missing in April 2015.
  Kendall, C.H., "The Electromagnetic Theory of Light" 30pp 1903 box 90, folder 985 was reported missing in April 2015.
  Allen, Wyatt H., "Electrical Units and Standards" 29pp, box 89, folder 946 was reported missing April 2015
  - Abbe, Harry A., "Mechanical Stokers" 12pp, 1905 (Box 89, Folder 943)
  - Adams, Ernest. K., "An Automatic Recording and Intermediate Reproducing Device for Pianos and Organs" 18pp, 1896 (Box 89, Folder 944)
  - Adler, Sidney, "The Loading of Telephone Circuits with Pupin Self-Induction Coils" 8pp, 1905 (Box 89, Folder 945)
  - Allen, Wyatt H., "Electrical Units and Standards" 29pp, 1896 (Box 89, Folder 946)
    Allen, Wyatt H., "Electrical Units and Standards" 29pp was reported missing April 2015
  - Allerton, Robert W., "The Action of Gasoline Vapor in a Gasoline Engine" 14pp, 1902 (Box 89, Folder 947)
  - Augur, Robert Clayton, "The Westinghouse Automatic Airbrake" 52pp, 1887 (Box 89, Folder 948)
  - Bates, Clifford W., "Automobile Transmission Gearing" 17pp, 1905 (Box 89, Folder 949)
  - Beach, Harold Kenney, "Heating and Ventilating of Machine Shops" 33pp, 1904 (Box 89, Folder 950)
  - Bergen, Henry V., "Copyright in England up to the Case of Donaldson vs. Beckett in 1774" 51pp, 1895 (Box 89, Folder 951)
  - Bredt, E. Arthur, "Telephones and Telephony'' 23pp, 1897 (Box 89, Folder 952)
  - Brinley, Charles Edward, "Some Considerations of the Formulas deduced by the late Professor George Pratt Starkweather in his "Thermodynamic Relations for Steam" 15pp, 1901 (Box 89, Folder 953)
  - Broun, Raymond Lester, "Direct Current Versus Single Phase Alternating Current in the Electric Zone Connected with the Grand Central Station" 23pp, 1908 (Box 89, Folder 954)
  - Burgess, Henry Edwards, "The Advantages of Superheated Steam in the Steam Engine" 18pp, 1904 (Box 89, Folder 955)
  - Canada, Charles Eben, "The Electrification of Steam Railways " 18pp, 1904 (Box 89, Folder 956)
  - Canado, William Joseph, "Some Observations on the Expansion of Distilled Water and Chloride in Solution Near the Temperature 4 C" 57pp, 1902 (Box 89, Folder 957)
  - Cederberg, W. E., "The DeLaval Steam Turbine" 37pp, 1902 (Box 89, Folder 958)
  - Champlin, Franklin J., "The General Electric Company's Type K Series Parallel Railway Motor Controllers" 21pp, 1911 (Box 89, Folder 959)
  - Chang, Tatsemg, "An Outline of the Theory of Electromagnetic Waves" 22pp, 1909 (Box 89, Folder 960)
    Chang, Tatsemg, "An Outline of the Theory of Electromagnetic Waves" 22pp was reported missing in April 2015.
  - Clark, W.R., "The Dynamo" 16pp, 1899 (Box 89, Folder 961)
  - Clifton, L.T., "Alternate Currents" 67pp, 1895 (Box 89, Folder 962)
  - Collins, Clarence Lyman, "Electricity in Railroading" 26pp, 1896 (Box 89, Folder 963)
  - Colton, Roger Baldwin, "Experiment on Coefficient of Expansion of Glass" 11pp, 1908 (Box 89, Folder 964)
  - Corbet, Darral, "Hydraulic Transmission of Power" 11pp, 1905 (Box 89, Folder 965)
  - Cumins, Cloyd, "The Development of High-Tension High Efficiency Insulators" 24pp, 1911 (Box 89, Folder 966)
  - Dadourian, Haroutine M., "Cathode Rays" 32pp, 1903 (Box 90, Folder 967)
  - Daly, C. H. "Niagara Falls as a Source of Power" 22pp, 1894 (Box 90, Folder 968)
  - Davoud, Vahram Y., "Electric Power on Railway Truck Lines" 28pp, 1903 (Box 90, Folder 969)
  - DeForest, Edgar Alfred, "Modern Blast-Furnace and Coke-Oven Gas Engines" 20pp, 1906 (Box 90, Folder 970)
  - Dudley, S.W., "The Sources of Error in the Steam Engine Indicator Diagram" 39pp, 1900 (Box 90, Folder 971)
  - Fahy, Frank P., "The Submarine Telegraph" 30pp, 1902 (Box 90, Folder 972)
  - Fear, Lyle G., "The Lead Storage Battery" 20pp, 1908 (Box 90, Folder 973)
  - Fields, H.A., "The Poly-Phase Motor as Conceived by Tesla" 17pp, 1895 (Box 90, Folder 974)
  - Finch, Frank Richard, "The Williams Central Valve Engine" 21pp, 1904 (Box 90, Folder 975)
  - Gilbert, Harold Arthur, "The Influence and Elimination of the Products of Combustion in Gas Engines" 13pp, 1901 (Box 90, Folder 976)
  - Henderson, John Milton, "Transmission of Power by Belts" 28pp, 1899 (Box 90, Folder 977)
  - Hines, B. F., "The Synchronous Motor" 12pp, 1902 (Box 90, Folder 978)
  - Hitchcock, H. S., "Specific Inductive Capacity" 30pp, 1895 (Box 90, Folder 979)
  - Hsia, Yuan-li, "Vector Analysis and Electric Waves" 39pp, 1907 (Box 90, Folder 980)
  - Hughes, Frederick George, "Conveyors for Coal and Iron Ores" 28pp, 1900 (Box 90, Folder 981)
  - Hull, John Irving, "The Plant of the Niagara Falls Power Company" 15pp, 1908 (Box 90, Folder 982)
  - Hyde, W.A., "The Oscillatory Discharges in a Condenser Circuit" 20pp, 1901 (Box 90, Folder 983)
  - Kelly, Trumbull, "The Development of Modern Armor Plate" 8pp, 900 (Box 90, Folder 984)
  - Kendall, C.H., "The Electromagnetic Theory of Light" 30pp, 1903 (Box 90, Folder 985)
    Kendall, C.H., "The Electromagnetic Theory of Light" 30pp 1903 was reported missing in April 2015.
  - Kernan, Thomas, "Some Advantages of Alternating Currents" 32pp, 1895 (Box 90, Folder 986)
  - Lanphier, Robert C., "Long-Distance Transmission of Power by Electricity" 27pp, 1897 (Box 90, Folder 987)
  - Leeds, Norman, "Power Houses of Electric Railways" 20pp, 1895 (Box 90, Folder 988)
  - Leggett, Willis S., Jr., "The Secondary Battery" 21pp, 1906 (Box 90, Folder 989)
  - Leonard, Norman Alva, "Centrifugal Governors" 17pp, 1908 (Box 90, Folder 990)
  - Lewis, Henry Leroy, "Electron Theory" 24pp, 1909 (Box 90, Folder 991)
  - Limburger, Ernest A., "The Efficiency of Electric Traction" 16pp, 1895 (Box 90, Folder 992)
  - Lowe, Abbott Lawson, "On Single Phase Alternating Current Motors" 18pp, 1906 (Box 90, Folder 993)
  - Lowenberg, Laurent, "The Theory of the Transformer" 19pp, 1897 (Box 90, Folder 994)
  - Luker, Herbert, "On the Anatomy of Three West Indian Epiphytes" 9pp, 1901 (Box 90, Folder 995)
    Luker, Herbert, "On the Anatomy of Three West Indian Epiphytes" 9pp was reported missing in April 2015.
  - McCarn, Burtis B., "Blast Furnace Gas, Its Preparation and Use" 32pp, 1909 (Box 91, Folder 996)
  - McCrea, S.H., Jr., "Dressed Beef Shipping" 20pp, 1888 (Box 91, Folder 997)
  - McEwen, Lewis C., "The Submarine Cable" 15pp, 1898 (Box 91, Folder 998)
  - Miller, D.H., "Long Distance Transmission of Electrical Power" 14pp, 1904 (Box 91, Folder 999)
  - Mixer, George I., "Electrical Units and Standards" 17pp, 1895 (Box 91, Folder 1000)
  - Moran, E.E., "The Development of Electric Traction" 20pp, 1904 (Box 91, Folder 1001)
  - Morris, Armand Vanuxem, "Electric Traction" 21pp, 1897 (Box 91, Folder 1002)
  - Newton, F. E., "The Electromagnetic Theory of Light" 20pp, 1895 (Box 91, Folder 1003)
  - Norton, C.A., "Centrifugal Fans for Mine Ventilation" 23pp, 1903 (Box 91, Folder 1004)
  - Perry, Clarence Curtis, "On the Light Sensitiveness of Electrolytically Deposited Copper from a Solution Containing Ammonium Chloride" 10pp, 1904 (Box 91, Folder 1005)
  - Plimpton, S.J., "Hertz Wave Detectors as Applied to Telegraphy" 14pp, 1905 (Box 91, Folder 1006)
  - Pritchard, Harold T., "The Generation of Electrical Power at Niagara" 23pp, 1908 (Box 91, Folder 1007)
  - Quinlan, F.T., "Reinforced Concrete" 13pp, 1907 (Box 91, Folder 1008)
  - Reid, G. Harold, "The Long Distance Transmission of Electrical Energy" 34pp, 1901 (Box 91, Folder 1009)
  - (Rich, G.B.?), "Tesla's Contributions to Electrical Science", 1897 (Box 91, Folder 1010)
  - Sanford, C.H., "Transmission of Power by Compressed Air" 18pp, 1905 (Box 91, Folder 1011)
  - Saxon, Louis, "A Cable for the Propulsion of a Submarine Boat" 29pp, 1895 (Box 91, Folder 1012)
  - Schneider, A. I., "Shaft Governors" 27pp, 1902 (Box 91, Folder 1013)
  - Seeley, Alfred Bryant, "The Development of the Modern Wireless Telegraph System" 28pp, 1909 (Box 91, Folder 1014)
  - Seward, Herbert Lee, "Steam Steering Gears" 23pp, 1906 (Box 91, Folder 1015)
  - Shepard, William Kent, "Alternating Currents" 19pp, 1897 (Box 91, Folder 1016)
  - Sherwood, Edward J., "Losses of Energy in the Steam Engine" 27pp, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 1017)
  - Simpson, William Klein, "The Design and Construction of a Press for Packing Lubricant in Trolley Wheel Hubs" 14pp, 1905 (Box 91, Folder 1018)
  - Smith, Daniel S., "The Electric cell" 27pp, 1901 (Box 91, Folder 1019)
  - Smith, Frank Benjamin, "The Evolution of the Storage Battery" 21pp, 1896 (Box 91, Folder 1020)
  - Speidel, J. W., "Hertzian Waves" 28pp, 1900 (Box 91, Folder 1021)
  - Stilson, Clarence H., Jr., "Elements of Dynamo Designing" 11pp, 1897 (Box 91, Folder 1022)
  - Strobridge, William, "The Use of Superheated Steam in Steam Engines" 21pp, 1900 (Box 91, Folder 1023)
  - Thomas, A.M., Jr., "The Circulatory System of the Flounder" 33pp, 1897 (Box 91, Folder 1024)
  - Tracy, Joseph G. H., "Polyphase Motors" 25pp, 1896 (Box 91, Folder 1025)
  - Uhl, E. L., "Transmission of Energy by Alternate Currents" 27pp, 1894 (Box 92, Folder 1026)
  - Underwood, Louis E., "The Development of the Trolley System" 12pp, 1896 (Box 92, Folder 1027)
  - Vinten, E. Stiles, "Galvanometers" 22pp, 1896 (Box 92, Folder 1028)
  - Wakeman, Henry R., "The Induction Motor" 20pp, 1904 (Box 92, Folder 1029)
  - Walker, Elisha, "The Screw Propeller" 27pp, 1900 (Box 92, Folder 1030)
  - Waters, William J., "The Extraction of the Juice from Sugar Cane by Means of Mills" 26pp, 1909 (Box 92, Folder 1031)
  - Watson, D. B., "The Alternating Current Transformer" 21pp, 1899 (Box 92, Folder 1032)
  - Wells, Arthur C., "The Warming, Washing and Fitration of Air for Ventilation" 18pp, 1906 (Box 92, Folder 1033)
  - Wells, Frederic H., "The Induction Motor" 35pp, 1909 (Box 92, Folder 1034)
  - Wheeler, Dwight Clark, "The Development of the Steam Turbine" 25pp, 1904 (Box 92, Folder 1035)
  - Wheeler, L. P., "Standard arid Uniform Time" 33pp, 1894 (Box 92, Folder 1036)
  - Whitcomb, W.A., "Modern Views of Electricity" 15pp, 1895 (Box 92, Folder 1037)
  - White, George R., "The Electrification of Steam Railroads" 10pp, 1906 (Box 92, Folder 1038)
  - Winton, Robert P., "The Signal System in the Shore Line Cut in New Haven" 18pp, 1909 (Box 92, Folder 1039)
- Engineers Club, 1895-1918; Series VIII
  Series VIII, ENGINEERS CLUB 1895-1914, consists of two notebooks containing the club's constitution, minutes of meetings, yearly reports, lecture notices and notes, newscfippings, mailing lists, memoranda and financial records.
  The materials are organized by form.
  - Constitution, minutes, mailing list, accounts, 1895-1913 (Box 93, Folder 1040)
  - Constitution, minutes, historical notes, 1896-1914 (Box 93, Folder 1041)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, financial records, 1909-1918, undated (Box 93, Folder 1042)
- Class Records, 1869-1969; Series IX
  Series IX, CLASS RECORDS 1869-1969, contains correspondence and memorabilia from sixteen classes between 1869.-and 1908. The records of the Class of 1901 are most complete and are representative of the types of material found in other years. These include Class Secretary and/or Class Agent correspondence, financial records, biographical data and statistics on graduates, reunion material, photographs, slides and memorabilia.
  Arranged chronologically according to class year. Materials within each section are organized alphabetically.
  - Class of 1869s
    - Photographs
      - Buildings and Grounds
        - Buildings, unidentified (Box 94, Folder 1043 - 1044)
        - Buildings, interiors, identified (Box 94, Folder 1045)
        - Campus and twon grounds (Box 94, Folder 1046)
        - Campus characters (Box 94, Folder 1047)
      - Faculty
        - Faculty, identified (Box 94, Folder 1048)
        - Faculty, unidentified (Box 94, Folder 1049)
        - Group pictures, 1869 (Box 94, Folder 1050)
        - Porter, William T.: etching (Box 94, Folder 1051)
      - Students
        - Students, identified 1869s graduates (Box 94, Folder 1052)
        - Students, identified 1869s non-graduates (Box 94, Folder 1053)
        - Students, unidentified (Box 94, Folder 1054)
  - Class of 1874s
    - Correspondence, 1881 (Box 95, Folder 1055)
  - Class of 1876s
    - Fifty-year reunion booklet, 1926 (Box 95, Folder 1056)
  - Class of 1878s
    - Correspondence and report, 1918 (Box 95, Folder 1057)
  - Class of 1881s
    - Biographical data, 1906 (Box 95, Folder 1058)
    - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 95, Folder 1059)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1946 (Box 95, Folder 1060)
  - Class of 1882s
    - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 95, Folder 1061)
    - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 95, Folder 1062)
    - Correspondence, 1922 January-July (Box 95, Folder 1063)
    - Correspondence, notes, 1922-1932 (Box 95, Folder 1064)
    - Correspondence, 1922 August 24 (Box 95, Folder 1065)
    - Correspondence, 1925-1926 (Box 95, Folder 1066)
    - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 95, Folder 1067)
    - Correspondence between Chauncy P. Williams and E. L. Whittmore, 1926-1929 (Box 95, Folder 1068)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1936
      - A-F (Box 96, Folder 1069)
      - G-S (Box 96, Folder 1070)
      - T-Z (Box 96, Folder 1071)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1949
      - C (Box 97, Folder 1072)
      - D (Box 97, Folder 1073)
      - E-G (Box 97, Folder 1074)
      - H-L (Box 97, Folder 1075)
      - M-W (Box 97, Folder 1076)
      - X-Z (Box 97, Folder 1077)
    - Correspondence and Letterbooks, 1910-1930
      - 1910-1915 (Box 97, Folder 1078)
      - 1915-1920 (Box 98, Folder 1079)
      - 1920-1927 (Box 98, Folder 1080)
      - 1927-1930 (Box 99, Folder 1081)
    - Fiftieth Reunion Correspondence
      - General information, 1931 (Box 99, Folder 1082)
      - List and program, 1932 (Box 99, Folder 1083)
      - A-B, 1932-1938 (Box 99, Folder 1084)
      - C, 1932-1940 (Box 99, Folder 1085)
      - D, 1930-1940 (Box 99, Folder 1086)
      - E-F, 1932-1940 (Box 99, Folder 1087)
      - L, 1932-1940 (Box 99, Folder 1088)
      - M, 1930-1940 (Box 99, Folder 1089)
      - N, S, 1930-1937 (Box 99, Folder 1090)
      - T, 1930-1932 (Box 99, Folder 1091)
      - W, 1930-1932 (Box 99, Folder 1092)
      - Yale, 1930-1949 (Box 99, Folder 1093)
  - Class of 1883s
    - Alumni Fund Correspondence
      - 1907, 1909, 1912, 1920, 1923, 1925-1928 (Box 100, Folder 1094)
      - 1932-1939 (Box 100, Folder 1095)
      - 1940-1947 (Box 100, Folder 1096)
    - General Correspondence and Biographical Material
      - A-D, 1916-1946 (Box 100, Folder 1097)
      - E-N, 1916-1946 (Box 100, Folder 1098)
      - P-Z, 1916-1946 (Box 100, Folder 1099)
    - Reunion Information
      - General information, 1914, undated (Box 100, Folder 1100)
      - Fifteenth reunion, 1898 (Box 100, Folder 1101)
      - Correspondence re: Yale Bicentennial Celebration (eighteenth reunion), 1901 (Box 100, Folder 1102)
      - Twentieth reunion, 1903 (Box 100, Folder 1103)
      - Twenty-fifth reunion, 1908 (Box 100, Folder 1104)
      - Thirtieth reunion, 1913 (Box 100, Folder 1105)
      - Thirty-fifth reunion, 1918 (Box 100, Folder 1106)
      - Reunion register, 1918, 1919, 1923, 1925 (Box 100, Folder 1107)
      - Special reunion, 1919 (Box 100, Folder 1108)
      - Fortieth reunion: correspondence, 1923 (Box 101, Folder 1109)
      - Forty-fifth reunion: correspondence, 1928 (Box 101, Folder 1110)
      - Fiftieth reunion: correspondence, 1933 (Box 101, Folder 1111)
      - Fiftieth reunion: correspondence and photograph, 1933 (Box 101, Folder 1112)
      - Fifty-fifth reunion: correspondence, 1938 (Box 101, Folder 1113)
      - Report: correspondence re: error, 1940-1941 (Box 101, Folder 1114)
  - Class of 1888s
    - Correspondence re: alumni fund contributions and death of classmates, 1939-1942 (Box 102, Folder 1115)
    - Fiftieth reunion: correspondence, 1938 (Box 102, Folder 1116)
    - Scholarship Fund: correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 102, Folder 1117)
    - Sherman, P.T.: recollections and obituary, undated (Box 102, Folder 1118)
    - Shigemi, Shlukichi Dr.: correspondence re: the Doctor and the Shigemi Fund, 1928-1932 (Box 102, Folder 1119)
  - Class of 1890s
    - Biographical Data and Correspondence 1869-1890
      - A-C (Box 103, Folder 1120)
      - D-J (Box 103, Folder 1121)
      - K-M (Box 103, Folder 1122)
      - N-R (Box 103, Folder 1123)
      - S-Z (Box 103, Folder 1124)
    - Reunion Material (Box 103)
      - General information, 1900-1905 (Box 103, Folder 1125)
      - Cash and reunion record book, 1900-1901, 1905, 1910-1911, 1915 (Box 103, Folder 1126)
      - Record book of Harry B. Day, Secretary, 1846, 1900, 1905, 1915 (Box 103, Folder 1127)
      - Twentieth reunion, 1910 (Box 103, Folder 1128)
  - Class of 1897s
    - Pencil portrait by B.H. Quinan?, 1947 (Box 133)
  - Class of 1901s
    - Biographical Data and Notes
      - Biographical data and obituaries, 1948-1961 (Box 104, Folder 1129)
      - Class roll cards, undated (Box 104, Folder 1130)
      - Obituary notices, 1932-1946 (Box 104, Folder 1131)
      - Obituary notices, 1939-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1132)
      - Printed cards, undated (Box 104, Folder 1133)
    - Biographical Questionnaires
      - Biographies prepared from the questionnaires for aReunion Recordfor the thirtieth and thirty-fifth reunions (never published): A-H, 1938 (Box 105, Folder 1134)
      - Biographies prepared from the questionnaires for aReunion Recordfor the thirtieth and thirty-fifth reunions (never published): I-Z, 1938 (Box 105, Folder 1135)
      - Questionnaires for a combinedReunion Recordcovering the thirtieth and thirty-fifth reunions (never published): A-H, 1938 (Box 105, Folder 1136)
      - Questionnaires for a combinedReunion Recordcovering the thirtieth and thirty-fifth reunions (never published): I-Z, 1938 (Box 105, Folder 1137)
      - Questionnaires for a combinedReunion Recordcoveringthe thirtieth through the forty-fifth reunions (never published): A-C, 1946-1947 (Box 105, Folder 1138)
      - Ques tionnaires for a combinedReunion Recordcovering the thirtieth through the forty-fifth reunions (never published): D-M, 1946-1947 (Box 105, Folder 1139)
      - Questionnaires for a combinedReunion Recordcovering the thirtieth through the forty-fifth reunions (never published): N-Z, 1946-1947 (Box 105, Folder 1140)
      - Blank forms, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 1141)
      - Completed forms, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 1142)
      - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 105, Folder 1143)
    - Correspondence of Class Secretary and Class Agent
      - Alumni Fund Campaign: letters of gratitude to the class via the Class Agent David Breinig, thanking it for its generosity, 1960-1963, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 1144)
      - Andrews, Harold F. (1906s) (Box 106, Folder 1145)
      - Breinig, David, Class Agent to B.W. Kunkel, Class Secretary (some replies), 1964-1969 (Box 106, Folder 1146)
      - Form letters, 1949-1961, 1966, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1147)
      - List of freshmen in 1898 (Box 106, Folder 1148)
      - Marcus, William E.: monographs and correspondence, 1966, 1968, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 1149)
      - The 1901 News, 1924-1930, 1933 (Box 106, Folder 1150)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1963
      - A (Box 107, Folder 1151)
      - B (Box 107, Folder 1152)
      - C (Box 107, Folder 1153)
      - D (Box 107, Folder 1154)
      - E-F (Box 107, Folder 1155)
      - G (Box 107, Folder 1156)
      - H-J (Box 107, Folder 1157)
      - K-L (Box 107, Folder 1158)
      - M (Box 107, Folder 1159)
      - N-O (Box 107, Folder 1160)
      - P-Q (Box 107, Folder 1161)
      - R (Box 107, Folder 1162)
      - S (Box 107, Folder 1163)
      - T-V (Box 107, Folder 1164)
      - W (Box 107, Folder 1165)
      - Z (Box 107, Folder 1166)
    - Correspondence with Class Members and Widows
      - 1961-1962 (Box 107, Folder 1167)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 107, Folder 1168)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 107, Folder 1169)
      - 1967-1969 (Box 107, Folder 1170)
    - "Class Notes"
      - 1951-1957 (Box 108, Folder 1171)
      - 1957-1961 (Box 108, Folder 1172)
      - 1961-1969 (Box 108, Folder 1173)
      - Correspondence, 1968, undated (Box 108, Folder 1174)
    - Financial Records
      - Account book of class funds, 1922-1925 (Box 108, Folder 1175)
      - Account book of class funds, 1922-1943 (Box 108, Folder 1176)
      - Audit, 1922-1945 (Box 108, Folder 1177)
      - Correspondence, 1927-1933 (Box 108, Folder 1178)
      - Twichell, Burton P.: correspondence re: funds, 1923-1934 (Box 108, Folder 1179)
    - Reunion Correspondence
      - Hooker, Brian: poem, 1907 (Box 109, Folder 1180)
      - Thirtieth reunion, 1931 (Box 109, Folder 1181 - 1182)
      - Thirty-fifth reunion, 1936 (Box 109, Folder 1183 - 1184)
      - Thirty-fifth reunion: class register, 1936 June (Box 109, Folder 1185)
      - Fortieth reunion: booklet, 1941 (Box 109, Folder 1186)
      - Forty-fifth reunion, 1945-1946 (Box 109, Folder 1187)
      - Forty-fifth reunion: class register, 1946 June (Box 109, Folder 1188)
      - Fifty-fifth reunion, 1956 (Box 109, Folder 1189 - 1190)
      - Sixtieth reunion, 1961 (Box 110, Folder 1191)
      - Sixty-fifth reunion, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 1192)
    - Reunion Memorabilia
      - Twenty-fifth reunion: identification buttons and cards, 1926 (Box 110, Folder 1193)
      - Ties and armbands, undated (Box 110, Folder 1194)
    - Reunion Printed Volumes
      - Triennial Record, 1904 (Box 111, Folder 1195)
      - Sexennial Record, 1907 (Box 111, Folder 1196)
      - Decennial Record, 1911 (Box 111, Folder 1197)
      - Quindecennial Record, 1916 (Box 111, Folder 1198)
      - Vicennial Record, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 1199)
      - Twenty-fifth Reunion Record(1926), 1930 (Box 112, Folder 1200)
      - Reunion Groups(1904, 1907, 1911, 1916, 1921, 1926, 1931, 1936, 1941), 1946 (Box 112, Folder 1201)
      - The Second Twenty-Five Years of the Class of 1901, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 1202 - 1203)
      - Sixtieth reunion report, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 1204)
      - Sixty-fifth reunion report, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 1205)
    - Photographs
      - Class dinners, individuals and reunions, 1931, 1940, 1950, 1953 (Box 113, Folder 1206)
      - (Fortieth) reunion portrait, 1941 (Box 113, Folder 1207)
      - Forty-fifth reunion portrait, 1946 (Box 113, Folder 1208)
      - (Fiftieth) reunion portrait, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 1209)
      - Fifty-fifth reunion portrait, 1956 (Box 113, Folder 1210)
      - Sixtieth reunion portrait, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 1211)
      - Sixty-fifth reunion portrait, 1966 (Box 113, Folder 1212)
  - Class of 1902s
    - Scrapbooks
      - General: clippings, memorabilia, reunion material, photographs, 1902-1957 (Box 114, Folder 1213 - 1217)
      - Thirtieth reunion, 1932 (Box 115, Folder 1218)
      - Thirty-fifth reunion, 1937 (Box 115, Folder 1219)
      - Scrapbook cover, undated (Box 115, Folder 1220)
    - Photographs
      - Chemistry class, Highland dorm residents, unidentified, 1902, undated (Box 116, Folder 1221)
      - Class portrait, 1900 (Box 116, Folder 1222)
      - Reunions
        - Twentieth reunion, 1922 (Box 116, Folder 1223)
        - Twenty-fifth reunion, 1927 (Box 116, Folder 1224)
        - Thirty-fifth reunion, 1937 (Box 116, Folder 1225)
        - Fortieth reunion, 1942 (Box 116, Folder 1226)
        - Forty-fifth reunion, 1947 (Box 116, Folder 1227)
        - Informal reunion at the Yale Club, 1950 (Box 116, Folder 1228)
        - Fiftieth reunion, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 1229)
        - Informal reunion, 1954 (Box 116, Folder 1230)
        - Informal reunion, 1956 (Box 116, Folder 1231)
        - Fifty-fifth reunion, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 1232 - 1233)
        - (Informal reunion?), 1960 (Box 116, Folder 1234)
  - Class of 1906s
    - Men of Yale 1795-1966: dedicated to members of all the 1906 classes (Box 117, Folder 1235 - 1236)